Guide to the Tillie Olsen Papers, 1930-1990 M0667
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 2. Papers, 1930-1950
  - Subseries A. Miscellaneous Early Writings (incl. journals, etc.), circa 1930-1950's
    - Writings: During and after Stanford (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Writings: After Stanford - withdrawal time, 1956-57 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous writings:, circa 1950's (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous writings:, circa 1950's (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous writings:, circa 1950's (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Miscellaneous writings: ca. 1950's: (potential story) (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Miscellaneous writings: ca. 1950's: (potential story) (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Miscellaneous writings: ca. 1950's: (potential story) (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Miscellaneous writings: ca. 1950's: (potential story) (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Miscellaneous writings:, circa 1950's (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Miscellaneous writings:, circa 1950's (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Miscellaneous writings:, circa 1950's (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Miscellaneous writings:, circa 1950's (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Miscellaneous writings: ca. 1950's, Qualities of writers (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Journals/notebooks, (1930-1960); 30 volumes (Box 17)
  - Subseries B. Articles, Clippings, Bulletins, Mss's of Others, circa 1930-1959
    - Clippings: Olsen's prison sentence, 1930's (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Excerpts from striker's, 1930's; Mss of headlines (TLO's babysitter) (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Clippings, re. longshoreman's strike:, circa 1930's (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Clippings, re. longshoreman's strike:, circa 1930's (Box 18, Folder 4)
      (includes related poetry)
    - Clippings, re. longshoreman's strike:, circa 1930's (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Clippings, re. longshoreman's strike:, circa 1930's (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Clippings, re. longshoreman's strike:, circa 1930's (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Newsclippings and pamphlets:, circa 1940's (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Interview with Tillie Olsen re. meat shortage (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - CIO Articles and pamphlets (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - CIO Articles and pamphlets (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - FBI file:, 1944 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Clippings and bulletins:, circa 1950's (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Clippings and bulletins:, circa 1950's (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - MSS's by others (poems and stories):, circa 1930's (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - MSS's by others (poems and stories):, circa 1930's (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - MSS's by others (poems and stories): ca. 1930's, "And We Are Millions," 1933 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Transcript of speech (speaker and date unknown) (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Writings, 1924 (Ida Lerner); political platform for TLO's father (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - "The Hollywood Ten," newsclipping, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Series 3. Correspondence
  Series III, Correspondence, is divided into five distinct sections, with each section determined by the time period or content of the particular correspondence. All the correspondence is incoming except when noted in the listing as "outgoing."
  Series IIIa is personal correspondence written during the time period 1930-1950. This series is of particular interest because of the correspondence with such individuals as Robert Gehn, Arel Creel, Jeannette Gray, Marion "Dippy" Duve, and Malcolm Cowley.
  Series IIIb is personal correspondence from 1950-1990 arranged alphabetically by name. Included in this series are individuals such as Margaret Atwood, Kay Boyle, Rachel Blau DuPlessis, Dick Elman, Hanna Green, Ursula LeGuin, Lewis Mumford, Katherine Anne Porter, Adrienne Rich, May Sarton, Scott Turow, and Alice Walker.
  Series IIIc is also personal correspondence but arranged chronologically from 1960-1989. Series IIId consists of reader's responses to Tillie Olsen's writings along with invitations to talks, seminars, and workshops. Finally, Series IIIe is correspondence to and from publishers and general requests, i.e. publishing rights, permission to dramatize works, letters of recommendation, biographical information, etc.
  - Subseries A. Correspondence - Personal (incoming)
    - Early correspondence: Faribault, Minnesota, 1932 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Early correspondence: Faribault, Minnesota, 1930 - 1939 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Early correspondence, 1930 - 1939 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Early correspondence, 1930 - 1939 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Early correspondence, 1930 - 1939 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Early correspondence, 1930 - 1939 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Early correspondence, 1930 - 1939 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Early correspondence, 1930 - 1939 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Early correspondence, 1930 - 1939 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Early correspondence, Robert Gehn (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Early correspondence, Arel Creel (incoming & outgoing) (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Early correspondence, Jeannette Gray (and miscellaneous) (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Early correspondence, Marion "Dippy" Duve (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Early correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1930 - 1939 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Early correspondence, re. Olsen's prison term, 1934 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Early correspondence, Al Hayes, 1935 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Early correspondence, High School (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Early correspondence (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Early correspondence, Office of War Information, Aug, 1943 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Early correspondence, 1940 - 1950 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Early correspondence, Donald Bigham, Sacramento County Jail, 1934 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Early correspondence, Malcolm Cowley, 1930 - 1939 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Early correspondence, Malcolm Cowley, 1930 - 1939 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Subseries B. Correspondence: Personal/General (Individual): Incoming, 1950 -1990:
    - Miscellaneous "A" (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Aberlin, Betty, (1964-1980) (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Alanoraig, Nancy, circa 1978-1979 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Alta/Shameless Hussy, circa 1974-1977 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Amatnick, Kathie (Sarachild), circa 1975-1981 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Anderson, Maggie, (1978-1986) (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Appleton, Sally, circa 1975-1976 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Arnold, Jane (with outgoing, circa 1976 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Atwood, Margaret, (1978) (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Ausubel, Bobbi (with outgoing, circa 1976-1977 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous "B" (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Bacon, Ernst, (1959-1963) (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Ballantyne, Sheila, circa 1988 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Barolini, Helen, circa 1982 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Berg Collection: Individuals (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Bingham, Sallie, circa 1979 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Boucher, Sandy, (1966-1987) (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Boucher, Sandy, (1966-1987) (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Boucher, Sandy, (1966-1987) (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Boyde, Blanche, (1973-1979) (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Boyle, Kay, (1988) (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Boynton, Grace, (1965-1986) (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Brandon, Dolores (ca. 1976) (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Breathitt, Mary Fran, (1973-1981) (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Brennan, Mave (n.d.) (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Bridges, Harry, (1974) (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Brindel, June Rachuy, (1981) (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Brown, Rosellen, (1976-1984) (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Bryant, Dorothy, (1979-1980) (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Bunting, Polly (ca. 1973) (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Miscellaneous "C" (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Cahill, Susan, (1976-1986) (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Childress, Alice, (1966-1984) (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - Clark, Ann Friend, (1979-1980) (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Cliff, Michelle (ca. 1973-1981) (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Cohen, Florence (with outgoing, ca. 1979-1981) (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Cohen, Jody (ca. 1977-1978) (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Coiner, Constance (ca. 1982-1986) (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Conroy, Lynne (with outgoing, ca. 1977-1980) (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - -------, ------- (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Cooper, Jane (ca. 1974-1986) (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Cornillon, Susan - see Koppleman, Susan (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Cumming, Patricia, (1976-1978) (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Cuomo, Joe, (1977-1979) (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Davis, Hope, (1963-1980) (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - DeFord, Miriam Allen, (1966) (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - De Patta, Margaret (ca. 1950's) (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - De Salvo, Louise A. (ca. 1980-1986) (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Dranow, Rachel, (1980) (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Duncan, Erika, (1967-1988) (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - DuPlessis, Rachel Blau, (1978) (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Elman, Dick, (1960-1983) (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Elman, Dick, (1960-1983) (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - English, Dierdre, (1976-1979) (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Ettinger, Elzbieta (ca. 1970's) (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Finke, Leondo (ca. 1981) (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Fisher, Elizabeth, (1971-1974) (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Foley, Margaret, (1973) (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous "G" (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Gilgun, John, (1960-1979) (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Goedicke, Patricia, (1970-1971) (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Goldfarb, Sidney, (1965) (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Gottlieb, Annie, (1968-1981) (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Greenberg, Joanne, (1984-1989) (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Griffin, Susan (ca. 1970-1977) (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Grumbach, Doris (with outgoing, 1978) (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Guerard, Albert, (1972) (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous "H" (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Hanna, Gayle, (1970-1978) (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Harstad, Grace, (1975-1981) (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Hedges, Elaine, (1970-1989) (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Heffernan, Helen (re. Margaret Heaton), (1960) (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Henry, Dewitt, (1977) (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Homley, Elaine, (1972-1975) (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Hopkins, Glen (with outgoing, 1975-1976) (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Hughes, Mary Gray, (1969-1989) (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Hughes, Mary Gray, (1969-1989) (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Hughes, Mary Gray, (1969-1989) (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous "J" (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Janows, Jill, (1978-1979) (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Jong, Erica (n.d.) (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous "K" (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Kallet, Marilyn, (1980-1982) (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Kaye, Melanie, (1975-1980) (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Keeble, John, (1980) (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Kizer, Carolyn, (1967-1975) (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Klepfisz, Irena (Lena), (1979-1980) (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Kolodny, Annette, (1980) (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Konecky, Edith (Edie), (1973-1984) (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Koppleman, Susan (with outgoing, 1972-1977) (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Kramer, Julie, (1976-1978) (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Kumin, Maxine, (1963-1969) (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Miscellaneous "L" (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - LeGuin, Ursula, (1978-1979) (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Levertov, Denise ("An Open Letter in Reply to Lee Richards, 1970") (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Limmer, Ruth, (1979) (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Lish, Godon, (1962-1978) (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous "M" (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous "M" (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - MacDowell Art Colony: Individuals (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - MacDowell Art Colony: Individuals (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - MacDowell Art Colony: Individuals (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - MacDowell Art Colony: Individuals (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - MacDowell Art Colony: Individuals (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - MacDowell Art Colony: Individuals (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - MacShane, Frank, (1970-1983) (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Mackenzie, Midge (with outgoing, 1978-1981) (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Mackenzie, Midge (with outgoing, 1978-1981) (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Malamud, Bernard (ca. 1965-1967) (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Marchant, Mary, (1977-1978) (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Mathewson, Mrs. Rufus (n.d.) (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Meehan, Maude, (1982-1983) (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Meyer, Howard, (1973-1980) (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Meyer, Odette, (1976-1989) (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Miller, Nolan, (1956-1978) (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Millet, Kate, (1974) (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Miner, Valerie (with outgoing, 1979-1986) (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Minty, Judith, (1980-1985) (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Mirrielees, Lucia and Edith, (1956-1957) (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Mitzger, Deena, (1978-1986) (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Pineda, Marrianne - see Tovish, Marrianne (Box 26)
    - Moers, Ellen, (1973-1978) (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Moffat, Mary Jane, (1973-1989) (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Morgan, Ellen, (1971-1977) (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Motjabai, Grace, (1978) (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Mumford, Lewis, (1965) (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Murray, Michele (with outgoing, 1973-1974) (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Myers, Margaret (ca. 1960-1961) (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous "N" (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Naiman, Adeline, (1974-1980) (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Nardie, Marcia (with outgoing, ca. 1960's) (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Nason, Thelma, (1969-1987) (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Ng, Fae Myenne, (1988) (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Olsen, Tillie (outgoing, 1970-1984) (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Orr, Elaine, (1982-1986) (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Ostrikes, Alicia (photocopy of correspondence, 1990) (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Ozick, Cynthia (with outgoing, 1966-1978) (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Ozick, Cynthia (with outgoing, 1966-1978) (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous "P" (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Paley, Grace, undated (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Papanek, Hanna, (1964-1981) (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Park-Fuller, Linda (with outgoing, 1978-1983) (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Partridge, Denny (with outgoing, circa 1977 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Phillips, Jayne Anne, (1978-1986) (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Phillips, Jim, circa 1959-1960 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Piercy, Marge, (1977-1978) (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Porter, Katherine Anne (photocopy of correspondence, 1978) (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Miscellaneous "R" (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Radcliffe Institute: Individuals (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Radcliffe Institute: Individuals (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Randall, Margaret, (1986) (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - Reeves, Nancy, (1968-1980) (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - Rich, Adrienne, (1976-1985) (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Rich, Adrienne, (1976-1985) (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Rich, Adrienne, (1976-1985) (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Roemer, Michael, circa 1977 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Rogers, Linda, circa 1977 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Rosen, Norma, (1972-1986) (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Rosenfelt, Debby, (1974-1986) (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Ruddick, Sally (with Pamela Daniels, circa 1977 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Russ, Joanne, (1972-1979) (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous "S" (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Sarton, May, (1969) (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Saxton, Ruth, (1978-1979) (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Schimps, Erich F., (1975) (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Schuchman, Brina-Rae, (1977-1978) (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Scowcroft, Richard (Dick) (with outgoing, 1956-1973) (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Sextant, Anne, circa 1962-1970 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Seyerstad, Per, (1979-1981) (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Shanahan, Thomazine (Timmy) (with outgoing, 1971-1979) (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Showalter, Elaine, (1970-1981) (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Skotnes, Pearl, (1978-1980) (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Smith, Alice, (1970-1984) (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Spivakovsky, Erika, (1970-1981) (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Stanberg, Susan, (1979-1983) (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Starkman, Elaine, (1977-1978) (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Sternburg, Janet, (1974-1978) (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Stone, Ruth, (1975-1981) (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Swan, Barbara, (1964-1979) (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Swan, Barbara, (1964-1979) (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - Sweeney, John (Jack), (1964) (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Tanenhaus, Beverly, (1975-1976) (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Treuhaft, Decca, (1973-1989) (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - Tovish, (Marrianne, Red, and Margo), (1965-1986) (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Tovish, (Marrianne, Red, and Margo), (1965-1986) (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Turow, Scott, circa 1970's (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Untermeyer, Louis, (1965) (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Ward, Theadora, (1953-1981) (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Walker, Alice, (1970's-1983) (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Walker, Alice, (1970's-1983) (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Walker, Alice, (1970's-1983) (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Walker, Alice, (1970's-1983) (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Walker, Mike, (1962-1964) (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Washington, Mary Helen, undated (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Waterman, Ray, (1976-1982) (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Wilder, Annie, (1962-1986) (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Wilder, Annie, (1962-1986) (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Wilder, Annie, (1962-1986) (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Willison, Toni, (1972-1980) (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Wilson, J. J., (1974-1985) (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Winters, Janet (ca. 1974) (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Winters, Sylvia (n.d.) (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Wong, Nellie, (1982-1983) (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Woolf, Cynthia, (1982) (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Wright, Sarah & Michael, (1975-1987) (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Yalom, Marilyn, (1982-1984) (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Yamada, Mitsui, (1975-1988) (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Zucker, Jack, circa 1969 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Unknown (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Green, Hannah (ca. 1970's) (Box 2223)
  - Subseries C. Correspondence: Personal/General (Chronological)
    - Chronological correspondence, Jul-Oct, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Chronological correspondence, Undated circa 1970's (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Chronological correspondence, Nov-Dec, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Chronological correspondence, Undated circa 1970's (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Chronological correspondence, Jan-Mar, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Chronological correspondence, Undated circa 1970's (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Chronological correspondence, Apr-Sep, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Chronological correspondence, Oct-Dec, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1961 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Chronological correspondence, Jan-Mar, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1962 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Chronological correspondence, Apr-Sep, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1983-1989 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1963 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Chronological correspondence, Oct-Dec, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Chronological correspondence, Undated circa 1980's (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1964 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1967 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Chronological correspondence, Jan-Sep, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Chronological correspondence, Oct-Dec, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Chronological correspondence, Jan-Jul, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Chronological correspondence, Undated circa 1971 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Chronological correspondence, Aug-Dec, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Chronological correspondence, Undated circa 1972 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Chronological correspondence, Undated circa 1960's (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Chronological correspondence, Undated circa 1971-1973 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Chronological correspondence, Undated circa 1960's (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Chronological correspondence, Undated circa 1970's (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Chronological correspondence, Jan-Jul, 1970 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Chronological correspondence, Undated circa 1970's (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Chronological correspondence, Aug-Dec, 1970 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Chronological correspondence, Undated circa 1970's (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Chronological correspondence, Jan-Mar, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Chronological correspondence, April - July, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - Chronological correspondence, Aug-Dec, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Chronological correspondence, Jan-Jul, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Chronological correspondence, Aug-Dec, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Chronological correspondence, Jan-Mar, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Chronological correspondence, April - June, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - Chronological correspondence, No Date (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Subseries D. Correspondence: Readers Responses/Invitations
    - Responses to Readings (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Responses to Readings (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Reader's responses to Silences (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Reader's responses to Silences (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Reader's responses to Silences (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Reader's responses to Silences (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Reader's responses to Silences (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Reader's responses to Silences (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Reader's responses to Silences (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Reader's responses to Silences (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Silences: letters from writers, artists, friends (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Reader's responses (Women who have lived Silences) (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Reader's responses (Women who have lived Silences) (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Corr. re. Harper's publication of Silences, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Reader's responses to Tell Me a Riddle (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Reader's responses to Tell Me a Riddle (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Reader's responses to Tell Me a Riddle (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Reader's responses to Tell Me a Riddle (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Reader's responses to Tell Me a Riddle (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Reader's responses to Tell Me a Riddle (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Reader's responses to Tell Me a Riddle (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Reader's responses to Tell Me a Riddle (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Response to Life in The Iron Mills (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Invitations to Talks/Seminars/Workshops (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Invitations to Talks/Seminars/Workshops (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Invitations to Talks/Seminars/Workshops (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Invitations to Talks/Seminars/Workshops (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Invitations to Talks/Seminars/Workshops (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Invitations to Talks/Seminars/Workshops (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Invitations to Talks/Seminars/Workshops (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Invitation to the Northern California Women's Facility, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Responses to Readings (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Subseries E. Correspondence: Publishers/Requests
    - Antioch Review (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Anvil (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Antlantic Monthly (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Bantan Books (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Brandt & Brandt (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Controversy (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Covici, Friede Inc. (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - D. Appleton - Century Company (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Delacorte/Dell/Delta (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Direction (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Dubuque Dial (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Elaine Markson Literary Agency (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Elaine Markson Literary Agency (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Faber & Faber (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Farrar & Rinehart (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Fight (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Godmother Productions: Tell Me a Riddle film (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Harpers (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Houghton Mifflin (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Knopf (Box 33, Folder 1)